{
    "id": "9c449abd35244b019bb3ef417221c403",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He was called Christy .................................................... his grandfather who had died in the civil war.",
            "description": "Call after = be named after somebody",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "after",
                "around"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cdfa385d331746d4b2b30ef9af9eea15"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is not much ............................................ air-conditioners during the winter season.",
            "description": "Call for = demand\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "call in",
                "call on",
                "call for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6634eea7bb0f4710b33691ee1ae7725b"
        },
        {
            "question": "This remarkable achievement ........................................... a celebration.",
            "description": "Call for = demand, require",
            "answers": [
                "calls in",
                "calls off",
                "calls for",
                "calls out"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d27aca4f1da948ff8a363bab060e8c1a"
        },
        {
            "question": "This spike in property prices forced us to ........................................... buying a new apartment.",
            "description": "Hold off = delay",
            "answers": [
                "hold off",
                "hold on",
                "hold to",
                "hold with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3c55c8f1e7ad47468fab5d393e98edfe"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you ............................................. people who live together before they get married?",
            "description": "Hold with = accept or agree\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "hold on",
                "hold out on",
                "hold with"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d4287da85cd84fde81bf1de3c3eac62e"
        },
        {
            "question": "We were ................................................. by the traffic jam.",
            "description": "Hold up = delay while traveling",
            "answers": [
                "held out",
                "held up",
                "held on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ba41a49b1691466e996af9e5e0a760ac"
        },
        {
            "question": "She likes to .................................................... old clothes for some strange reason",
            "description": "To hold onto something is to keep it longer than necessary",
            "answers": [
                "hold together",
                "hold off",
                "hold onto"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9ebba10009c14ba38a0eb787e53d1f05"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................................ your hands. I am going to inspect your finger nails",
            "description": "To hold out is to extend in front of you",
            "answers": [
                "Hold on",
                "Hold out",
                "Hold off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d24271886cf248809d2dd29b76e0f46b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The strikers .................................................. until the management agreed to give them what they wanted.",
            "description": "To hold out is to resist / protest. ",
            "answers": [
                "held up",
                "held off",
                "held out"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5ba7aa1560de4dafb6eaf87c0a6b529a"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................................. the rope. I am going to pull you up.",
            "description": "To hold onto something is to grip it tightly",
            "answers": [
                "Hold onto",
                "Hold over",
                "Hold on",
                "Hold at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fa469bcde790452a9d8a1b3386949879"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is very ill. She can't .............................................. even water.",
            "description": "To keep food down is to keep it in the stomach without vomiting.",
            "answers": [
                "keep at",
                "keep in",
                "keep down"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f2a0aef5037f44afa0ceeaa275bedea0"
        },
        {
            "question": "The police ............................................ the protesters .............................................. by blocking the road.",
            "description": "To keep somebody back is to keep them at a safe distance.",
            "answers": [
                "kept, back",
                "kept, away",
                "kept, at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0274d7ed70734ccd8c57e4118f5c783a"
        }
    ]
}